Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/shahzaib-pervez-19414195 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Inventory Management
Inventory Control
Time Management

Shahzaib Pervez

Inventory Manager at Pakistan Law House

Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan

Summary

Experienced Inventory Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the legal services industry. Skilled in Microsoft Excel, Customer Service, Microsoft Office, Administration, and Human Resources. Strong operations professional with a Master's degree focused in Logistics, Materials, and Supply Chain Management from Iqra University (Official).

Experience

Pakistan Law House Inventory Manager September 2018 - Present (6 years 3 months) Pakistan Chowk

Medicam Group Of Companies Procurement Officer January 2018 - August 2018 (8 months) Karachi

Tectutive (Pvt) Ltd.
Customer Service Representative
June 2014 - September 2014 (4 months)

Education

Iqra University (Official)

Master's degree, Logistics, Materials, and Supply Chain

Management · (2018 - 2020)

Iqra University (Official)

Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA), Business Administration and Management, General · (2013 - 2017)